《人人都爱催眠蛙》
原创作者：催眠蛙
改编作者：催眠蛙
改编自催眠蛙的原创角色
主演：催眠蛙
人人都爱催眠蛙
监制：催眠蛙
Everybody Loves Hypnotoad
拍摄于某直播厅几千里深的地下
Was filmed thousands miles below a live studio audience.
第 3H312 集
亚马逊历险记
*宁静的小屋*
编剧：催眠蛙
导演：催眠蛙
催眠蛙万岁
执行制作人：催眠蛙
噢
Aww.
好诶
Yeah!
黛娜瑞亚
今晚闪电速配
人人都爱催眠蛙
Everybody Loves Hypnotoad
广告之后 马上回来
will return after these messages.
人人都爱催眠蛙 由盖瑞音乐公司赞助播出
Everybody Loves Hypnotoad was brought to you by: Gary's All Purpose  Music.
你非要听音乐的话 就听盖瑞公司的吧
When you must listen to music, make it Gary's.
TORGO牌脂粉 可直接用于臀部
Torgo's powder. Apply directly to the buttocks.
精华卡路里
Calorie Substance.
由催眠蛙倾情推荐
Recommended by: Hypnotoad
催眠蛙的客人都处于
Guests of the Hypnotoad stay at
历史悠久的"人牢山庄"
historic Cragmont Human Cage,
在那里 他们被迫互相打斗供他取乐
where they are forced to fight for his amusement.
*宁静的小屋*
啊
Wow.
人人都爱催眠蛙 第一季
Everybody Loves Hypnotoad. Season One.
现已发售DVD
Now available on DVD.
包含了全部365集
You get all 365 episodes.
还有从未公开的镜头
Plus never before seen footage
还有导演和编剧的点评
Commentary from the writers and directors
催眠蛙万岁
All Glory to the Hypnotoad
还有很搞笑的花絮
And hilarious outtakes.
剪掉
Cut!
哈哈哈
Ha ha ha...
有可能造成内出血
May cause internal bleeding.
今晚十一点
Tonight at 11,
提前预览催眠蛙全新的重磅医疗剧
A sneak peak at Hypnotoad's hard pounding new medical drama:
《催眠诊断》
Diagnosis Hypnosis
圣-危机 医院
*宁静的小屋*
Zito兄弟的秋千学院
黛娜瑞亚
速配进行中
当我数到五十 你就会醒过来
On the count to 50, you will awaken
感觉全然陌生 什么都不记得
feeling refresh and remembering nothing.
抱歉 我得从头开始
I'm sorry. I have to start again.
人人都爱催眠蛙 下集预告
Next time on Everybody Loves Hypnotoad.